https://www.piercemfg.com/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
Pierce Manufacturing Inc. Privacy Statement
Effective date: April 2020
Pierce Manufacturing Inc. with its corporate office located in Wisconsin, USA and our affiliated businesses (collectively, "Pierce Manufacturing" or "us") are committed to being responsible custodians of the information you provide us and the information we collect in the course of operating our business.
Pierce Manufacturing takes your personal privacy seriously. This Privacy Statement describes how Pierce Manufacturing, as a data controller, may collect, use and share information, particularly in association with the operation of our main website (www.piercemfg.com) and other websites, providing products and providing services.
This Privacy Statement describes:
The types of information Pierce Manufacturing collects
How Pierce Manufacturing uses the information Pierce Manufacturing collects
How Pierce Manufacturing may share the information Pierce Manufacturing collects
Third-Party services and content
Protection and storage of the information Pierce Manufacturing collects
Your choices and rights in the European Union
Changes to this Privacy Statement
Use of Cookies
Data generated by the operation of our products and the use of our services
The types of information Pierce Manufacturing collects
Pierce Manufacturing collects data when you provide it to us, use our products or use our services, for instance by visiting our website, contacting us, meeting us at a trade show, operating our products, using our services or by entering into a contract with us. "Personal data" is any information that can be used to identify you or that Pierce Manufacturing can link to you, for instance your name and email address. Pierce Manufacturing may automatically collect certain information when you use, access, or interact with us via our websites, for instance via browser settings or cookies, or while operating our products or use our services. Pierce Manufacturing may also collect information from other sources, such as social media platforms that may share information about how you interact with our social media content, or if you interact with us via our social media accounts.
All personal data you provide to Pierce Manufacturing or that we (automatically) collect is voluntarily. However, without providing certain data, for instance your email address, we may not be able to respond to your request or deliver our services.
Our websites, products and services are generally not directed to children under 16. Pierce Manufacturing does not knowingly collect personal data from anyone under 16 without parental consent. If you become aware that Pierce Manufacturing has collected personal data from a child under the age of 16 without parental consent, please contact our EU data representative so Pierce Manufacturing can take appropriate action.
How Pierce Manufacturing uses the information Pierce Manufacturing collects
Pierce Manufacturing will only process personal data where it has a legal basis to do so. Pierce Manufacturing may use the information Pierce Manufacturing collects:
To enter into a contract or settlement, or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract or settlement (such as account registration);
To respond to your inquiries, to provide you with services that you request, to communicate with third parties in the handling of claims or complaints, to maintain business administration records and prevent fraud, which is our legitimate interest;
To keep records and administration on how services were provided, claims and complaints were handled, including the documents underlying such services, claims and complaints, which is our legitimate interest;
To understand how people use our websites, products and services, to operate, maintain and improve our website, products and services, to send direct marketing communications, which is our legitimate interest;
To comply with legal obligations applicable to Pierce Manufacturing, such as respond to legal process or requests for information issued by government authorities or other third parties.
EU personal data will be transferred to and stored in the US at a server of Pierce Manufacturing in compliance with the European General Data Protection Regulation. If you have questions about the appropriate safeguards Pierce Manufacturing has in place or wishes to obtain a copy of such safeguards, please contact our EU data representative.
How Pierce Manufacturing may share the information Pierce Manufacturing collects
Pierce Manufacturing and its affiliated entities share information with each other or with third-party service providers for general business purposes pursued by Pierce Manufacturing, such as internal administration, billing, claim handling and services, and providing you or your organization with services.
Pierce Manufacturing and its affiliated entities may share information with third party data controllers (including law enforcement agencies and potential transaction partners) where Pierce Manufacturing and its affiliated entities have a legal basis to do so.
Pierce Manufacturing does not sell, rent, or otherwise share personal data with information that reasonably identifies you for their independent use except as expressly described in this Privacy Statement or when Pierce Manufacturing has a legal basis to do so, for instance with your prior consent.
If Pierce Manufacturing transfers EU personal data to a recipient outside the European Union, it will only do so in compliance with the European General Data Protection Regulation. If you have questions about the international transfers of your personal data or the appropriate safeguards Pierce Manufacturing has in place or wishes to obtain a copy of such safeguards, please contact our EU data representative.
Third-party services and content
Our websites, products and services may include integrated content or links to content provided by third parties (such as social media platforms). This Privacy Statement does not, unless specifically noted, address the privacy, security, or other practices of the third parties that provide such content. We recommend considering the privacy policies applicable to third parties prior to visiting those websites, operating those products or using those services.
Pierce Manufacturing engages third parties that support the operation of our websites, products and services such as analytics providers. These third parties may use technologies to track your activities over time and across different websites and online platforms. Please click here for more information.
Protection and storage of the information we collect
Pierce Manufacturing deploys administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to safeguard the information that Pierce Manufacturing collects. However, no information system can be 100% secure. This means that Pierce Manufacturing cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal data. Moreover, Pierce Manufacturing is not responsible for the security of information you transmit to us over networks that Pierce Manufacturing does not control, including the Internet and wireless networks.
Pierce Manufacturing retains the information Pierce Manufacturing collects in an identifiable form as reasonably necessary and only for as long as required to fulfill the purposes for which Pierce Manufacturing collects the information and to comply with our legal obligations.
Your choices and rights in the European Union
Where we process your personal data on the basis of your consent, you may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting our EU data representative. Where we process your personal data on the basis of our or a third party's legitimate interest, you may object to such processing at any time by contacting our EU data representative.
Pierce Manufacturing encourages you to contact us to update or correct your information if it changes or if you believe that any information that Pierce Manufacturing has collected about you is inaccurate. You can also ask us to see what personal data we hold about you, to rectify or erase your personal data, or to port your personal data and you may tell us if you object to or want to restrict our use of your personal data. If you would like to discuss or exercise such rights, please contact our EU data representative. You can also use this link to lodge a complaint. If you are not satisfied about the manner in which Pierce Manufacturing handles your complaint, you may also lodge a complaint with the competent data protection authority.
For information about the choices you may have in regard to our use of cookies, please click here.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
Pierce Manufacturing may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. The effective date of the current Privacy Statement is noted at the top of this page. Pierce Manufacturing encourages you to periodically review this page. You will be informed separately if needed, for instance should we process your personal data for other purposes than set out in this Privacy Statement.
Use of Cookies
Pierce Manufacturing collects certain information by automated means when you visit our websites. By collecting this information, Pierce Manufacturing learns how to best tailor our websites to our visitors. Pierce Manufacturing collects this information through various means such as “cookies,” “web beacons”, and “IP addresses” as explained below.
Like many companies, Pierce Manufacturing uses “cookies” and “web beacons” (also known as internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs) on our websites. Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit certain websites. Web beacons allow us to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third-party. Pierce Manufacturing uses the information collected from these technologies to compile reports and help us improve the website.
For example, a cookie might tell us whether you have visited us before, the number of visitors to the website, which site a visitor has come from, the pages they visited, and to help us identify site features in which you may have the greatest interest. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site.
Pierce Manufacturing also collects IP addresses. An IP address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our websites, Pierce Manufacturing may view and/or store the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. Pierce Manufacturing uses this information to determine the general physical location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our website visitors come from. Pierce Manufacturing also may use this information to enhance Pierce Manufacturing's websites.
More information about the cookies we use on our websites is set out in the table below.
Cookie
Provider
Purpose
Expiry
fr
facebook.com
Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.
3 months
tr
facebook.com
Facebook conversion tracking pixel to measure efficiency of viewed or clicked ads to help show targeted ads in the future.
Session
collect
google-analytics.com
Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices an d marketing channels.
Session
NID
google.com
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
6 months
__cfduid
hs-analytics.net
Used by the content network, Cloudflare, to identify trusted web traffic.
1 year
__ptq.gif
hubspot.com
"Sends data to the marketing platform Hubspot about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels."
Session
bcookie
linkedin.com
Used by the social networking service, LinkedIn, for tracking the use of embedded services.
2 years
lidc
linkedin.com
Used by the social networking service, LinkedIn, for tracking the use of embedded services.
Session
_ga
piercemfg.com
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
2 years
_gat
piercemfg.com
Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate
Session
_gid
piercemfg.com
Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.
Session
hubspotutk
piercemfg.com
Keeps track of a visitor's identity. This cookie is passed to the marketing platform HubSpot on form submission and used when de-duplicating contacts.
10 years
__hssc
piercemfg.com
Collects anonymous statistical data related to the user's website visits, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded. The purpose is to segment the website's users according to factors such as demographics and geographical location, in order to enable media and marketing agencies to structure and understand their target groups to enable customized online advertising.
Session
__hssrc
piercemfg.com
Collects anonymous statistical data related to the user's website visits, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded. The purpose is to segment the website's users according to factors such as demographics and geographical location, in order to enable media and marketing agencies to structure and understand their target groups to enable customized online advertising.
Session
__hstc
piercemfg.com
Collects anonymous statistical data related to the user's website visits, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded. The purpose is to segment the website's users according to factors such as demographics and geographical location, in order to enable media and marketing agencies to structure and understand their target groups to enable customized online advertising.
2 years
_hjIncludedInSample
piercemfg.com
Determines if the user's navigation should be registered in a certain statistical place holder.
Session
@@History/@@scroll|#
twitter.com
Remembers users last scroll position on each webpage to assist in backwards navigation.
Persistent
p.gif
typekit.net
Used to track the use of the specialist fonts we use on our website and does not track your data or your personal information.
Session
Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all our website features. Some browsers offer a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signal whereby you may indicate your preference regarding tracking and cross-site tracking. Although Pierce Manufacturing does not currently employ technology that recognizes DNT signals, Pierce Manufacturing will only process your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
Our websites also use web analysis services such as Google Analytics, in order to better understand your use of our websites and how we can improve them. The information generated by these services is anonymous and does not include personal data about you. The anonymous information collected through the use of these services is not combined with any personal data you may have explicitly chosen to share with us. The providers’ ability to use and share information collected by these services about your visits of our websites is restricted by terms of use and the providers’ privacy policies. To get a better understanding of how these providers may use the anonymous data collected on our websites, you may review, as an example, Google’s policy on this matter here. You can also opt-out of Google advertising features through your ad settings, or by visiting this page.
Data generated by the operation of our products and the use of our services
You acknowledge that data may be generated during the operation of our products, for instance during the initial manufacturing process, during the transport of our products, by dealers or by end customers. You also acknowledge that data may be generated through the use of our services. You agree to be bound by the terms and conditions governing such activities, including those specifically listed below.
Oshkosh Data Systems Agreement
HAAS, Inc.
© 2020 Pierce Manufacturing, Inc.
Registered Trademark of Pierce Manufacturing Inc. Appleton, WI, USA an Oshkosh Corporation Company
